(Leonard:)Hear, hear.
Cheers.
(Howard:)You realize that's the first
time we've ever done that
(Howard:)without having
to listen to Sheldon tell us
(Howard:)why it's called a toast?
(Priya:)Why is it
called a toast?
(Leonard:)Oh, the ancient Romans
(Leonard:)put spiced toast
in their punch bowls.
(Raj:)Sheldon tells it better.
(Leonard:)He kind of does.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)Aw, hell, I miss him.
(Penny:)So, where do you guys
want to go dancing?
(Bernadette:)We were hoping
you'd know a place.
(Amy:)Yes, perhaps somewhere
packed tightly
(Amy:)with young, beautiful bodies
(Amy:)sweating and writhing
against each other
(Amy:)in a glorious orgy
of the flesh.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, I know that place.
(Penny:)What do you think?
(Amy:)That should display enough
of your bosom
(Amy:)to attract a new mate,
or a hungry infant.
(Penny:)Okay, let's go
through this one more time.
(Penny:)Just because
Leonard has a new girlfriend
(Penny:)does not mean I need to go out
and hook up with some guy.